Zarrar Ali

Lahore District, Punjab, Pakistan



zarryfosh@gmail.com



03068519866



linkedin.com/in/zarrar-ali-9859701aa

Summary

I am an HR Professional with much potential. I am majorly involved in Technical recruitment, headhunting, and Full recruitment cycles. I also have a bit of taste in L&D, and employee engagement activities. I have 1 year of experience, and with my experience and skill set, I am sure that I can touch the stars and go beyond.

Experience

Junior HR Generalist

Contour Software

Dec 2021 - Present (8 months +)

- 1) Managing whole recruitment cycles.
- 2) Carrying out all routine HR tasks.
- 3) Assisting in Employee Engagement plans.
- 4) Generating weekly and monthly HR reports.
- 5) Handled different situations with a professional approach.
- 6) Responsible for extensive technical recruitment.
- 7) IT-related recruitment.
- 8) Assisting L&D programs.
- 9) Human Capital lead generation / Lead generation / HR sourcing.
- 10) Headhunting.
- 11) Updating employee data and creating reports.
- 12) Managing all HR tasks on ATS and HRMIS.
- 13) Assisting in orientation and onboarding process.
- 14) Assisting in the organization's policy implementation.
- 15) Job Description Development
- 16) Sourcing
- 17) Talent Management

Human Resources Trainee

Contour Software

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021 (4 months)

ш

Human Resources Trainee

Asia Foods

Jun 2021 - Aug 2021 (3 months)

- 1) I managed all the HR and operations matters effectively.
- 2) Assured all the labor laws.
- 3) Managed and solves queries of employees.
- 4) Assisted in supply chain functions.
- 5) Designed training programs.

- 6) Provided reports to senior management.
- 7) Carried out all the tasks effectively



Human Resources Intern

Paragonoverseasconsultants

Mar 2019 - May 2019 (3 months)

I did all the responsibilities as an HR intern

- 1) Updating company databases by inputting new employee contact information and employment
- 2) Screening potential employees' resumes and application forms to identify suitable candidates to fill company job vacancies.
- 3) Organizing interviews with shortlisted candidates.
- 4) Posting job advertisements to job boards and social media platforms.
- 5) Removing job advertisements from job boards and social media platforms once vacancies have been filled.
- 6) Assisting the HR staff in gathering market salary information.
- 7) Assisting in the planning of company events.
- 8) Preparing and sending offer and rejection letters or emails to candidates.
- 9) Coordinating new hire orientations.
- 10)Responding to staff inquiries regarding HR policies, employee benefits, and other HR-related matters.

Education



University of the Punjab

Bachelor of Science - BS, Human Resources Management and Services 2017 - 2021

Licenses & Certifications



Microsoft foundation - Peak Solutions College

Skills

College Recruiting • Human Resources (HR) • Microsoft Excel • Recruiting • Labor and Employment Law • Employee Learning & Development • Global Talent Acquisition • Talent Management • head hunt Employee Relations